这个周末 你们在此
During your weekend here, you will explore ways,
将通过瑜伽 呼吸运动及其他心灵活动
through yoga, breathing, and other mindful practices,
跟自己和跟伴侣重新建立联系
to reconnect with yourself and your partner.
另外 只需少许捐款
Also, for a small donation,
我们现场的萨满巫医即可治愈你的轮穴
we have an on-site shaman who can heal your chakras.
少许捐款 听起来像是轮穴诈骗
Small donation? Sounds like a "Chakra con".
你应该要关机的
You're supposed to turn that off.
-抱歉 是工作 -这还关乎婚姻呢
- I'm sorry. It's work. - ?Okay, so is a marriage.
我们大老远跑来
You know, we traveled all this way.
你至少应该认真对待吧
The least you could do is take this seriously.
抱歉 你说得对
I'm sorry. You're right.
天啊 刚才那顿破早餐要55刀
Oh, my God, that -- that crappy breakfast was $55.
-就点亚麻籽和浆果 -是啊
- For flax and berries. - Yeah.
我以为事先一次性收费 之后就全包了
I thought this was supposed to be one fee up front, all in.
我倒希望你"全包式"投入 米奇尔
I wish you were all in, Mitchell.
抱歉 我是 从现在开始
I'm sor-- I am. Starting...now.
好了
Okay. ?
不是我手机响
That wasn't me.
我邀请了西藏颂钵来发出回响
I have invited the Tibetan Singing Bowl to ring,
提醒我们降低音量
reminding us to all turn down the volume
在静默中找到美
and find the beauty in silence.
很不幸
That was unfortunate.
抱歉 我们隔壁正好是皇家[队]
My apologies. We happen to be next door to the Royals.
天啊 我们刚狂看完皇室剧《王冠》
Oh, my God, we just binged "The Crown".
哪些皇室成员 威廉和凯特吗
W-W-Which royals? William and Kate?
还是哈里和《诉讼双雄》妹
Harry and the "Suits" girl?
事实上是堪萨斯城皇家队 他们正在春训
Actually, it's the Kansas City Royals. Spring training,
他们的训练场地就在隔壁
their practice field is next door.
我从小就是皇家队粉丝 看他们进行春训
Growing up a Royals fan, it was always my dream
一直是我的梦想
to see them at spring training.
于是我决定 等静修结束
So, I just decided, after the retreat was over,
我就过去看看
I'm just gonna swing by,
要个签名什么的
you know, grab an autograph,
也许在经理耳边说些建议
maybe whisper an opinion in the manager's ear,
被发现本人极具棒球头脑
be discovered as a great baseball mind.
然后洋基队就会来找我
Then the Yankees would come calling,
再然后我就不得不在热爱的球队
and then I'd have to choose between the team I love
和高薪之间做选择
and the -- the big payout.
现在想这些有点太着急了
But I'm getting ahead of myself.
无须担心 这是他们最后一天训练
Not to worry. This is their last day of training,
他们今晚就走了
and they leave tonight.
-不好意思 我有问题 -你说
- Excuse me, question. ?- Yes.
你好 请问我们会否有机会
Yes, hi. Will we have an opportunity to explore
自行探索这个美丽的庭院
these -- these beautiful grounds on our own?
当然 明天日落时
Absolutely. Tomorrow at sunset.
进行完山羊瑜伽后
After goat yoga.
天啊 还能更衰一点吗
Oh, my God! Can it get any worse?!
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
我生乔的时候都没哼那么大声
I grunted less when I was giving birth to Joe.
你只是推出6磅半 我可是撑起220磅
You were pushing six and a half pounds, I'm pushing 220.
你穿了更年轻的衣服
You're dressing younger.
你在锻炼身体
You're exercising.
今早你只吃了一份早餐
You only had one breakfast this morning.
-那个淫妇是谁 杰 我要杀了她 -冷静点
- Who is she, Jay? I'll kill her. - ?Relax, would ya?
我只是想保持身材
I'm just trying to get in shape.
好吧 不过快点
Okay, but hurry, because we have to go
我们还要去生日派对那接乔
and pick up Joe at the birthday party.
等一下
Wait a minute.
你做这么多就是因为这个吗
Is that what this is all about --
亨利的爸爸
Henry's father?
我不明白你为何如此不安
I don't understand why you're so insecure
就因为他比你年轻
just because he's younger,
比你强壮 比你粗犷
stronger, and more rugged than you are.
悠着点 我在努力只吃一份早餐了
Go easy. I'm working on only one breakfast.
乔一天到晚说他新朋友的爸爸
Joe won't shut up about his new friend's dad.
"亨利的爸爸好爷们哦" 谁在乎啊
"Henry's dad is so tough". Who cares?
他在几部《谍影重重》里当过特技替身
He was a stunt double in a couple of "Bourne" Movies.
从乔第一次去他们家
From the first time Joe went over there,
那家伙就不停地想证明自己有多酷
that guy's been trying to prove how cool he is.
乔 走了
Joe! Let's go!
小心
Heads up!
-什么鬼 -耶
- What the hell?! -Yeah!
他是杰森·伯恩
He's Jason Bourne!
那都是演的
That's make-believe.
马特·达蒙才是杰森·伯恩
Matt Damon's Jason Bourne.
小时候 我觉得我爸是最酷的人
Growing up, I thought my dad was the coolest.
那让我对自己也感觉良好
And that made me feel good about myself.
我是说 我努力赶上他
I mean, I try to stay with it.
没错 瞧瞧你 你还有智能手表呢
Exactly! Look at you, you even have a smart watch.
对 这玩意告诉我何时站起来
Yeah, the damn thing tells me when to stand up,
何时呼吸
when to breathe.
你的体重指数是...
Your body mass index is --
没人问你
Nobody asked!
哪个有更多染色体 土豆还是人类
Which have more chromosomes, potatoes or humans?
人类 对吧
Humans, right?
居然是土豆
Potatoes?!
小疯杯 还有你教不了我们的事吗
Oh, Krazy Kups, what can't you teach us?
你做这些都是为了让海莉男朋友觉得你厉害吗
Are you doing all this to impress Haley's boyfriend?
海莉在跟一个天才天体物理学教授谈恋爱
Haley's dating this genius astrophysics professor
不知怎的 他让她变聪明了
who's somehow making her smarter
因为上周 我说冥王星是行星
because, last week, I called Pluto a planet
结果海莉嘲笑我
and Haley laughed at me.
同情傻子那种笑
In pity.
-海莉耶 -海莉
- Haley. - ?Haley.
傻妹海莉
Haley.
我们该认为海莉跟教授能合适吗
Do we think that Haley is suited to a professor,
我觉得他跟傻汉比较合适呢
because I more saw her with a Gilligan type?
别这样 很多幸福的情侣
Come on, now. Lots of happy couples
智商都不在一个境界
aren't the exact same level of smart.
这倒是真的 我俩就行得通
That's true. We work.
是啊
Yeah.
等等 你说我俩就行得通
Wait. When you say, "We work,"
你是觉得你比我聪明 还是我比你聪明
do you think you're smarter than me or I'm smarter than you?
我想我够聪明到不跟你讨论这个
I think I'm smart enough not to have this conversation.
老天
Oh, my God!
你就这么想 你认为你比我聪明
You do! You think you're smarter than me!
好啊 天才 你有多少项专利
Okay, hotshot. How many patents do you have?
挠头器[第3季第9集] 阿司匹林枪
Headscratcher TM, Aspirin Gun,
能让开车人士不再发脾气的礼貌汽车喇叭
Polite Car Horn that'll put an end to road rage.
不好意思三连
Excuse me, excuse me, excuse me.
在这顿午餐前能不能先别争论这个
Can we just not get into a whole thing before this lunch?
什么午餐 我刚吃了个派
What lunch? I just ate a pie.
你姐姐在跟一个天体物理学教授交往
Your sister is dating a professor of astrophysics,
他今天要来见我们
and he's coming here today to meet us.
真好 有人跟我聊天了
Oh, good, someone to talk to.
我受够为了你们俩傻子而特意降低水平了
I'm tired of dumbing it down for you chuckle-heads.
比尔 你出发了吗
Bill, are you on your way?
待在车里 我到外面找你
Stay in the car. I'll meet you outside.
海莉开始跟阿尔文交往后 我挺难受的
It was hard for me when Haley started dating Arvin,
他可是我的教授和科学英雄
my professor and science hero and...
好吧 我还暗恋他
okay, fine, crush.
我很难过 跑回家了 然后可能太过放纵了
I was so upset, I went home, and I may have overindulged...
吃了很多贝果
on Bagel Bites.
没事 你安全了
It's okay. You're safe.
但你得跟我走
But I'm gonna need you to come with me.
你也没必要...
I don't really think you need --
好吧 他就像超级英雄
Okay. He was like a superhero.
那是你爸爸吗
Is that your dad?
一个英俊
A beautiful...
但智商欠奉的超级英雄
not-so-smart superhero.
我最不想要的就是费诺曼教授
The last thing I wanted was Professor Fennerman
发现我在跟一个笨蛋约会
finding out I was dating a dummy.
一个贴心 轮廓分明的笨蛋
A sweet, chiseled dummy.
艾丽克丝 你没说过你有个消防员男朋友啊
Alex, you didn't mention you've got a firefighter boyfriend.
是啊 很棒
Yeah! It's great.
"看我灭了你 火" 我们得走了
"Take that, you fire". We gotta go.
但你父母刚邀我留下吃午餐
Oh, but your parents just invited me to stay for lunch.
赚到啦
Score!
顺便说一下 你比海报上看起来年轻多了
By the way, you look way younger than your poster.
我们真的该走了 不然...
We really should get going before we --
会赶不上行程计划 对吧
we miss our plans and stuff, right?
-嗯 -是吧
- Yeah. - ?Uh, yeah...
艾丽克丝 我不知道你要一起吃午餐
Alex! I didn't know you were joining us for lunch.
不 不
Oh! No, no.
我朋友跟我有安排了 不能取消
My friend and I have some plans we really can't get out of.
不 我可以晚点再给你看《烈火雄心》
Oh, no, I could totally just show you "Backdraft" later.
是我哥的影碟 他都不知道我拿走了
It's my brother's DVD. He doesn't even know I took it. So...
爸爸妈妈 这是阿尔文
?Mom, Dad, this is Arvin.
阿尔文你好 很高兴认识你
Hello, Arvin. It's a pleasure to meet you.
没错 你可是我们家接待的第一位担任过
Yes, you are the first TED Talkin' science superstar
TED演讲嘉宾的科学超级巨星
we've ever had in our house.
只要我是超级巨星而不是超新星就好了
Well, as long as I'm a "Superstar" and not a supernova.
你们都不知道自己在笑什么
You don't even know what you're laughing at.
-我懂了 -我更懂
- I get it. - I got it more.
我没听懂 但你的口音像《王牌大贱谍》的主角
I don't get it, but, uh, you sound like Austin Powers, man.
亨利的爸爸为孩子们办的生日派对
Wow. Henry's dad did such a great job
真棒啊 对吧
with the birthday party for the kids, huh?
左一句亨利爸爸 右一句亨利爸爸
"Henry's dad". "Henry's dad".
我可是带乔到宽银幕影院看过《非洲女王号》
I took Joe to see "African Queen" in CinemaScope.
又见面了 杰
Oh, hey. Good to see you again, Jay.
-你好 -你好 我是克莱
- Hi. - Hi, I'm Clay.
我想跟你握手 但我手受伤了
I'd shake your hand, but I'm a little banged up.
我今早从五层高的大楼摔下来 落到网子上
I fell out of a five-story building this morning, into a net.
他今早从床上摔下来
?He fell out of bed this morning.
老婆
Hey, honey.
下来打个招呼
Come down and meet these guys.
嗨
Oh, hey!
欢迎 我是珍妮 亨利的妈妈
Welcome. I'm Jenny, Henry's mom.
我们是乔的爸妈 杰和歌洛莉亚
Joe's parents -- Jay, Gloria.
你好 歌洛莉亚
Hi. ?Gloria.
妈妈 亨利的妈妈爬墙速度超快的
Mama! Henry's mom just did the wall so fast!
你也试试
You try it.
我今早已经辛苦爬上这双高跟鞋了
Oh, I climb already into these heels this morning.
我今天运动量够了
It's too much for me today.
-我要再爬一次 -好的
- I'm going up again! - Okay.
我以前也很爱穿这种鞋子
Oh, I used to love wearing shoes like that.
但穿军靴行军两年后
But after marching around in combat boots for two years,
我跟我的脚约好 我再也不会伤害它们
I made a deal with my feet I would never hurt them again.
我美丽的太太被派驻到伊拉克两次
My beautiful wife did two tours in Iraq.
歌洛莉亚 你也差不多啊
Oh. ?Wow, Gloria, you're not that different.
昨天 她同一个货架逛了两次
Yesterday, she did two tours of a sales rack.
救命 我爬太高了
Help! I'm too high!
来吧 跳下来 我会接住你
Oh. ?Go ahead, just jump, buddy. I'll catch ya.
可你有坐骨神经痛
But your sciatica!
交给我
I'm on it.
有什么可急的 有安全绳
What is the hurry? He's on a rope.
-她可真能借机耍帅 -是啊
- She's making quite a meal out of this. ?- Yeah.
好小子
Attaboy.
谢谢你 珍妮 你太酷了
Thank you, Jenny. You're so cool.
快看 歌洛莉亚 她救了他
Ah, look at that, Gloria. She saved him.
就像她救了美国一般
Just like she saved America.
我们能再吃点蛋糕吗 是珍妮做的
Can I have some more cake? Jenny made it.
我过去总给我的中队做吃的
I used to cook for my squadron.
你做了这么多厉害的事
You've done so many great things
可以没完没了说给我们听
that you keep telling us about.
我们到了 感官剥夺池
Here we are -- our sensory deprivation tanks
能让你与世界隔离
will disconnect you from the world
联结自我
and connect you with yourselves.
这看起来有点像棺材
Okay, so, this looks a little coffin-y.
我说不好 因为我丈夫
So, I'm not so sure. About my husband.
他去年做核磁共振时恐慌发作了
He had an MRI last year, and he sort of freaked out.
所以你们有没有大点的
So, do you have anything bigger,
例如室内泳池或家庭型的水池
like, an indoor pool or a family tank?
米奇尔 我没事
Okay, Mitchell, I-I'm fine.
我们是来进化成长的
We're here to evolve and grow...
漂浮时间是一小时
So, the float lasts for one hour,
大部分人会体验到一种深层的放松状态
during which most people simply experience a deep, relaxed state.
大部分人 那其余的人呢
Most people? W-what about the rest?
他们体验到什么了
W-what do they experience?
这个盖子上是抓痕吗
Okay, a-are these scratches on this lid here?
别这样 米奇尔
Oh, come on, Mitchell.
逆境中绽放的花朵
The flower that blooms in adversity
是最珍稀最美丽的
is the most rare and beautiful of all.
说得真好
Very well put.
那不是他的话 是《花木兰》里的
He didn't make that up. It's from "Mulan".
我们女儿逼我们看了上千遍
Our daughter made us watch it a thousand times.
我发脾气了 好吧 或许我们该漂一下
I -- Well, I'm lashing! Okay, maybe we should just float.
-没错 我们漂浮吧 -好
- Yeah, let's just float. - ?Yeah, okay.
好的
Okay.
我在里面试着放松了 我真的试了
I tried to relax in there, I really did.
但太困难了
But it was difficult.
我想是因为我当时觉得
I-I guess because I felt like I was, um --
该怎么说
Oh, what's the word?
要死了
Dying.
但我挺过了那个阶段
But I got past that,
结果开始回味我犯过的每一个错误
only to start reliving every mistake I have ever made,
例如我去了一场奥斯卡派对
like when I went to an Oscar party and I said
在一群毒舌基佬面前念错"贝蒂·戴维斯"
"Bett" Davis in front of a room full of vicious gays.
说实话 唯一能让我坚持住的原因
Honestly, the only thing that kept me in there
就是知道小卡就在我隔壁
was the knowledge that Cam was right next door.
皇家队加油 我爱你们
Go Royals! I-I love you!
那是个周密的计划
It was a solid plan --
我就去看一眼 拍点照片
just go for a quick peek, take some pictures,
赶回来 往头发上泼点水
run back, splash some water in my hair,
"米奇尔 漂浮真让人放松啊"
"Oh, Mitchell, isn't floating so relaxing?"
-接住了 -接得好
- Got it! - Nice catch.
接得真好
Oh. ?That was good.
我的天 布列特先生
Oh, my gosh. Uh, M-mr. Brett.
我不知道您会在这
I didn't know you would be here.
叫我乔治
Hi. Call me George.
-乔治 -你好吗
- Oh, George. ?- Yeah, how are ya?
我很好 我叫卡梅隆
Uh, good. My name's Cameron.
很高兴认识你 小卡
Nice to meet you, Cam.
很高兴认识您 我一直是您的粉丝
Nice to meet you. Been a fan for --
您介意我拍张照片吗
Hey, do you mind if I get a picture?
完全不 完全不
Not at all. Not at all.
三百美元 怎么样
300 bucks, how's that sound?
我退休了
I'm retired.
-三百 -我开玩笑的
- 300? ?- I'm just kidding.
-快来 不要钱 -好
- Come on, it's free. - Okay -- Ow!
太好了 拍好了
Alright. ?There it is.
-拍好了 -好啊
- There they are! ?- There ya go!
我不想占用您太多时间
Well, listen, I don't want to take up too much of your time.
-太感谢了 -我有的是时间
- Thank you s- - ?I got all the time in the world.
我又不上场 我只是教练
I'm not playing. I'm just coaching.
-那好 -快来
- Okay. - ?Yeah. Come here.
我给你讲讲松焦油门的事
Let me tell you the story about the Pine Tar game.
你想听吗
You wanna hear that?
-当然 -快来
- Sure. ?- Come on.
-好的 -但我先给你讲讲
- Okay. ?- But first, let me tell you about --
我从前一晚的晚饭讲起
I'm gonna tell you about dinner the night before.
你肯定是那个天才男友
You must be the genius boyfriend.
大伙都那么叫我
That is what the guys call me.
他们总那么叫
They're always, like, you know,
"天才" 我就说"大伙"
"Hey, genius". I'm like, "Hey, guys".
告诉我 有没有外星人
So, tell me, are there aliens?
你认真的吗 百分之百有
You kidding? 100%.
我就知道 等等 那僵尸世界末日呢
Oh, I knew it. Wait, and the zombiepocalypse?
哥们 我总对所有人说
Dude, I tell everyone,
"现在就开始培养对僵尸病毒的免疫力"
"Start building up an immunity to zombie bites. Now".
和你聊两句我收获良多
I'm so glad we talked.
抱歉我刚才得去接电话
Um. Sorry for the interruption.
一切还好吗
Everything okay?
简单来说 是的
Well, the short story is, yes.
展开来说 我用了职业生涯大部分时间
The long story is, the theory on which I've based
来研究的理论刚刚被证明是错误的
much of my career has just been disproven.
什么 你的真空能量密度理论
What? Your Vacuum Energy Density Theory?
我很遗憾
I'm-I'm so sorry.
我也是 那是我最支持的密度理论
Me, too. That was the density theory I thought really worked.
真的吗 菲尔 你的第二支持的理论是什么
Really, Phil, what was your second choice?
这都是研究过程的一部分 不是吗
Well, that's all part of the process, isn't it?
而我的理论也让别人的理论无效了
My theory actually invalidated someone else's.
那人跳楼了
He jumped off a building --
非常戏剧化
just very dramatic.
但我是英国人 所以别担心
But, well, I'm British. So, no worries.
什么菜这么香
What smells so good?
是鸡肉
Uh. Uh, it's the chicken!
比尔 你是消防员
So, Bill, you are a firefighter?
是的 我最喜欢的三件事是帮助他人
Yeah, my three favorite things are helping people,
滑竿和在大卡车上待着
sliding down poles, and hanging off trucks,
所以我想不如就拿这个当事业吧
so I figured might as well make a career out of it.
幸好你最喜欢的三样东西
Well, it's good that your favorite things
不是氯仿 布基胶带和没有窗口的货车
weren't chloroform, duct tape, and windowless vans.
克莱尔 这个笑话是说他是绑匪
Claire, the joke is he'd be a kidnapper.
我听懂了
I got it.
要知道 菲尔过去以为
You know, Phil used to think
那个词是"鸭子"[音似]胶带
it was "duck" tape.
鸭子
Like, duck.
克莱尔没看懂《爱乐之城》的结局
Claire didn't understand the ending of "La La Land".
抱歉 他们平时不是这样的
Sorry. They're not normally like this.
很显然他们在争论某件事
Clearly, they're going through something
连这么重要的午餐都不能休战一会
they can't even drop for one important lunch.
他们在争论谁更聪明
They're arguing over who's smarter,
而这事只有一个方法能解决
and there's only one way to settle it.
改天去找婚姻顾问解决吗
Another time, in the presence of a marriage counselor?
不 头脑大战
Nope. Brain Battle.
不 不 我们现在不能玩这个
No. No, we're not doing that right now.
我很抱歉 阿尔文 我们真不该这样
I'm so sorry, Arvin. We're being silly.
有多少位总统在职期间去世
"How many presidents died in office?"
-八位 -六位
- Eight. - Six.
正确答案是八位
The correct answer is eight.
见鬼 再问一个
Damn it. Give me another one.
六为什么害怕七
Why was six afraid of seven?
因为七"扒"九
'Cause seven, eight, nine.
它"扒了"九
Like he "ate" it.
《白鲸记》是谁所著
"Who wrote 'Moby Dick'?"
赫尔曼·曼斯特 赫尔曼·曼斯特
Herman Munster. Herman Munster.
-赫尔曼·麦尔维尔 -麦尔维尔
- Herman Melville. - Melville!
木星有多少颗卫星
"How many moons does Jupiter have?"
我可以回答这个问题吗
Oh, is it alright if I take this one?
不 不是的
Hmm? No, that's-that's wrong.
天王星才有67颗
67 is Uranus and...
木星是27颗 对吗 艾丽克斯
Jupiter's 27, right, Alex?
其实不是的
Actually, no.
但那只是个小错误
But it's a simple mistake, though.
你只是记反了
You just flipped them.
这太令人羞愧了不是吗
Well, this is mortifying, isn't it?
我有天体物理学的博士学位
I have a doctorate in astrophysics.
白痴
Idiot.
先是一个傲慢的瑞典人作废了我一生的研究
First, some puffed-up Swedes invalidate my life's work.
然后我败给了小水杯上的脑筋急转弯
And then I'm bested by a little bedtime gurgle cup!
对不起 我得自己静一静
I'm sorry. I'm going to need a moment.
67颗卫星 真是白痴
67 moons. What an idiot.
我只知道
Well, all's I know is
地球只有一个月亮[卫星]
the Earth only has one moon
我看过一部纪录片说我们根本没登月
and I saw a documentary and we didn't even land on it.
我的天 闭嘴吧
Oh, my God, stop talking.
你这样有点刻薄
You know, you're being kind of mean.
我也得自己静一静
I'm gonna need a moment, too.
这就是为什么我不带男友回家
This is why I don't bring boyfriends home.
你们邀请他来吃午餐之前怎么不问问我
Why didn't you ask me before inviting him to lunch?
保罗·纽曼在哪部电影中的角色
"This Paul Newman character
被称为"辣手"
had a 'cool hand'?"
-卢克[铁窗喋血男主] -答对了
- Luke! - ?Yep.
这道也算 也算
Counts! Counts.
亨利的爸爸单手攀岩 太帅了
Henry's dad climbed the wall with one hand! It was awesome!
他的事业全仰仗马特·达蒙
Yeah, well, his career rides on Matt Damon
不拍需要动脑子的艺术片
not doing any artsy, think-y movies,
所以亨利很可能
so I wouldn't count on Henry
很快就读不起你的学校了
going to your school much longer.
搞什么 我赶在红灯之前了
What the hell? I made that light.
老天 又一张罚单
Oh, geez. Another ticket.
亨利的妈妈会开坦克
Henry's mom drove a tank!
亨利的妈妈 亨利的妈妈
Henry's mom! Henry's mom!
你做什么 歌洛莉亚
What are you doing, Gloria?
我倒想看看亨利的妈妈这样做
I want to see Henry's mom do this!
他在追我们
Yay! He's chasing us!
我觉得这是个馊主意
This feels like a bad idea.
太晚了 这事情已经没有回头路了
Okay, too late, because I'm already committed!
心率过高 心率过高
Heart rate -- high. Heart rate -- high.
你打算怎么做 歌洛莉亚
What is the plan, Gloria?
我们要去商场
We're going to the mall!
现在知道我为什么用购物的事打趣你了吗
You know why I tease you about your shopping?
你这的确是病
Well, you do have a problem.
身子压低 不要动
Okay, get down and don't move.
这可不容易 我闻到肉桂面包店的味儿了
That's gonna be tough. I can smell Cinnabon.
你都去哪了
Where have you been?
我在水里多泡了一阵子 加强一下
I just stayed in the tank a little -- a little extra.
真是场太棒的经历了
How -- What a great experience.
与自己独处
Just being alone with yourself --
我完全没独处到
Oh, I was never alone.
我看到了每个欺负我的人
I-I saw the face of every bully,
重新经历每一次羞辱
I replayed every humiliation --
又要提念错贝蒂名字的事了吗
Is this about "Bett" Davis again?
我们当时刚看完电影《家有恶夫》
Okay, we had just watched "Ruthless People".
你弄混贝特·米德勒与戴维斯了 放手吧
You're thinking Midler. You gotta let it go.
我知道啦 我会尽量
I know. I'm -- I'm gonna try.
但尽管我在里面感到如此害怕
But as scared as I was in there,
我一直不断地想着
I kept thinking about how
你是唯一令我感到有安全感的人
you're the one person who makes me feel safe.
让我有动力想要当一个更好的丈夫
And it made me want to be a better husband... ?Aww.
要给你更多陪伴 给予你更多理解 来...
...and to be more present, to be more understanding, to --
为什么你的脸是红的
Why -- Why's your face red?
-是吗 -对啊
- Oh, is it? ?- Yeah.
可能是因为排出毒素什么的吧
Oh, just probably 'cause of the toxins, you know --
你的手臂也是 但只红到了...
And your arms, too, but only up to the --
你这不是农夫晒吗
You have a farmer's tan.
你忘了我跟你谈过用这个形容词的事了吗
What have I told you about that expression?
-我乡村人可以说... -天啊...
- I can say it... - ?Oh, my --
我知道你为什么晒伤了 你去看皇家队了
That's why you're burned. You went Royal watching!
我本来就打算看两眼就走 但乔治·布列特
I was only gonna stay for a second, but George Brett --
乔治·布列特硬拉着我
George -- George Brett cornered me.
你也知道我碰到名人时是啥德行
And you know how I am with famous people.
我拒绝不了他们
I can't say "No".
你还记得我因此在泳池泡了一整天
Remember when I spent the entire day at the pool
就因为一个小牌女明星吗
with Downtown Julie Brown?
你让我羞愧好陪你来
You shamed me into coming here
结果你把我独自丢在一碗内心创伤汤里吗
only to leave me soaking in a bowl of trauma soup?
你等一下嘛 你不是说要...
Okay, whoa, whoa. W-What happened about be--
要给予更多理解吗
being more understanding?
你居然还想把这事赖成我的错
I can't believe you're turning this into my fault.
太像你会做的事了 小卡
This is so like you, Cams.
两位 再次问好
Hello, again.
请跟随我来你们的冥想课
Please follow me to your guided silent meditation.
在我们开始之前
Before we begin,
大厨让我请大家放心
the chef has asked me to reassure everyone
丹贝绝对没有问题
that there's nothing wrong with the tempeh.
它吃起来就是那个味道
It's supposed to taste that way.
好了
Alright.
深呼吸 从鼻腔吸入
Deep breath. In through the nose.
从鼻腔吐出
Out through the mouth.
只有在静默中我们才能真正存在
Only in silence can we be truly present.
但请准备好
But be prepared --
杂念可能会浮现
errant feelings may arise.
焦虑 怀疑 怒火
Anxiety, doubt, anger...
再一次呼吸 让那些情绪
Now, take a breath and let those feelings pass
像天空的云朵般随风而去
like clouds in the sky.
紧绷的内心慢慢舒缓开来
The tension is melting away.
就是这样
That's it.
活在这
Live in this moment
平静与静止的时刻
of serenity and stillness.
我们太习惯了要不停地冲刺再冲刺
We're so accustomed to going, going, going.
但我们需要的是停下
But we need to just stop.
扪心自问这个重要的问题
Ask yourself the important questions.
你是在逃离那些难解的情绪吗
Are you running away from difficult feelings?
你在紧抓着小肚鸡肠的事不放吗
Are you holding on to petty grievances?
你有在做最好的自己吗
Are you being the best you?
现在找回原来的道路还不晚
It's not too late to find your way back.
回到光明
To the light,
回到原谅
to forgiveness,
回到爱
to love.
太神奇了
It was amazing.
虽然没用语言
There were no words,
但我能感到小卡
but I could feel Cam
为我们的争吵表示负全部责任
taking full responsibility for our fight.
完全没有语言 但米奇尔的眼神写了
Total silence, but Mitchell's eyes said,
"一切都是我的错"
"It's all on me".
就是"我错了 没有你我该怎么办啊"
You know, "I was wrong. What would I do without you?"
真是个太美妙的周末了
It was a beautiful weekend.
而且乔治·布列特给我的球签名了
Plus, George Brett signed my ball.
"给小卡 祝你万事如意 乔治·布列特
Oh, "To Cam, all my best wishes, George Brett.
附注 这事儿我们俩没完"
P.S. We are not done with this"?
米奇尔
Mitchell!
你在我的球上写字了吗
Did you write on my ball?!
比尔上哪去了
Hey, where's Bill?
我不知道 他估计在外面
I don't know. He's probably outside.
他焦虑的时候就喜欢爬东西
When he gets agitated, he likes to climb stuff.
午饭真是神经病啊 你敢相信爸妈会这样吗
That lunch was insane. Can you believe Mom and Dad?
不啊 但我也没想到你会这样
No, and, uh, I can't believe you either.
你对比尔太毒了吧
You're so mean to Bill.
你跟高魅力人群有仇吗
What do you have against hot people?
-我们是哪里对不起你了 -你说什么呢
- What did we ever do to you? - ?You lost me.
你摆明会甩了那男的
You're gonna blow it with that guy,
人家明明很好
and he's really nice.
你为什么要让人家觉得自己是白痴呢
Why do you have to make him feel so dumb?
行了 你根本就是不懂在瞎扯
Okay, you don't know what you're talking about.
我可懂了
Oh, yes, I do.
因为你对待他跟对待我都用同种方式
Because it's the same way you've always treated me.
超不爽
It sucks.
你知道阿尔文从不做什么事吗
You know what Arvin never does?
让我觉得自己比他笨
Makes me feel less smart than him.
比尔不是"天柴"俱乐部的又如何
So, who cares if Bill's not a member of Menses?
他好歹是你第一个交往过的
Look, this is the first boyfriend you've ever had
年龄与你相仿 有工作
that is age appropriate, employed,
而且长得不像在船上快死的人
and doesn't look like he's dying on a ship.
他不算是"男朋友"
I wouldn't say "Boyfriend".
他比较算是有罪恶感的快感
He's more like a guilty pleasure.
无论有没有罪恶感 好歹这是我第一次
Guilty or not, that's the first time I've ever heard you
形容一个男生"有快感"
describe a guy as a "pleasure".
比尔 对不起
Bill, I'm sorry!
没事的 宝贝
All good, babe.
你是我唯一扑灭不了的一把火
You're the one fire I can't put out.
还有油类火灾也挺难扑灭
Well, also grease is pretty tricky.
阿尔文
Arvin?
阿尔文 你好 你没事吧
Arvin, hi. Are you okay?
没事 我没事
Yeah. Oh, yes. Yes.
没事 我只是有点羞愧
Um...yes. I-I-I'm just a-a little embarrassed.
我们才是该感到羞愧的人
We're the ones who should be embarrassed.
我们把午餐搞得特别紧绷怪异
We just made lunch so tense and weird.
那个 我...
Yeah. ?Well, I'm --
我不是那么会接受失败
I'm not terribly adept at handling failure.
我的父母都是超高成就的学者
My parents are both overachieving academics --
一个是哲学博士与数学博士
a doctor of philosophy and a doctor of mathematics.
而我爸爸是医学博士
Wow! ?And Father is a doctor of medicine
与经济学博士
and doctor of economics.
抱歉 我自己摆脱这情绪就行了
I-I'm sorry. I just need to shake it off.
控制好情绪
You know, stiff-upper-lip it.
我没事的
Yeah, it's fine.
能不能假装刚才没有发生过
Can we just pretend it never happened?
不
No.
不 失败很让人难受
No, failure sucks.
感到难受很正常啊
It's okay to feel bad.
想不开心就不开心吧 吃点冰激凌
Yeah, wallow a little. Eat some ice cream.
白天喝酒也没事 这样才能缓过来啊
Day drink, that's how you come out the other side.
你们 你们就像是我父母的相反版本啊
You're -- You're like the inverse of my parents.
除了喝酒的部分一样
Except the drinking.
他们几乎整天都醉醺醺的
They're pickled most of the day.
你现在不在父母家嘛
Well, you're not in their house.
这里是邓菲家 我们可以失败
This is House Dunphy -- We fail here.
对啊 比如我们今天本来的目标
Right. I mean, today our whole goal
是要给你留下好印象 结果弄巧成拙
was to impress you. We made fools of ourselves.
我开了一家不停亏钱的魔术用品店 成千在亏
I have a magic shop that's bleeding money -- thousands.
-什么 -没事的
- What? ?- It's fine.
这是在干嘛[英腔]
Hey, what's all this, then?
我这口音是被你传染的吗
Oh, whoa. Did I get that from you?
我要变成麦当娜了吗
Am I becoming Madonna?
你的父母对我很好
Your parents were actually being quite lovely.
谢谢你们开导我
Thank you for taking the time.
或许我父母家的墙上
Oh, and my parents' walls may be adorned
挂满了各种学位证与奖项
with nothing but degrees and awards,
但他们的情商不足你们的十分之一
but they don't have one tenth of your emotional intelligence.
谢谢你的夸奖
Aww! ?Thank you.
但你觉得我们俩的情商是完全一样吗
But would you say it's an absolutely equal emotional...
如果要选谁比较高...
If you had to pick a winner --
好了 闭嘴
Okay, stop it.
太好玩了
That was so fun.
我的心砰砰跳
My heart is racing.
那又如何 我的智能手表打给我的心脏医生了
You? My watch dialed my cardiologist.
我从没逃过警察
I've never run from the cops before.
我也没有啊
Me either.
灯
Lights!
我都等不及要跟大家说你们多酷了
I can't wait to tell everyone how cool you guys are!
我们不酷 乔
We're not cool, Joe.
正常人不应该
That's not what people do
在警察叫他们靠边停时这么做
when a policeman pulls them over.
其实我们俩一点酷的地方都没有
In fact, there's nothing cool about us.
我们也不需要这么泼冷...
Well, I don't think we should be lumped into --
灯
Lights!
乔 世上还有很多比酷更重要的事
Joe, there are more important things than being cool.
比如什么
Uh, like what?
乔 重点是我们太爱你
Look, the point is, Joe, we love you too much
把你宠到你觉得做这样的蠢事是可以的
to let you think dumb moves like this are okay.
那我们现在该做什么
So, what do we do now?
我们要做正确的事
We're gonna do the right thing.
警官
Officer!
肉桂面包店在哪里啊
Where's Cinnabon?
不用想也知道 他们检举我用太多松焦油
Sure enough, they call me out for using too much pine tar.
我冲出去跟裁判大吵
I run out there and just go berserk on these umpires.
但大家记得...
But everybody remembers -- ?Ugh!
小心 这里是垒包
Watch out. That's a base. ?Yeah.
-这里是三垒 -三垒
- That's third base. - Third base.
我当年也是三垒手 还记得吗
That's where I used to play. You remember that?
当然 我们要来...
Yeah. Should we do --
所以你当年会站在这里
So, when you would stand here,
会保持一个运动员的...
you would just kind of basically be in an athletic --
-我当年打大学橄榄球 -你会站到这里
- I played college football... - ?You would get here.
会这么站在这里 然后念叨着
You would get right here like this and say,
"千万别打到我这边来"
"Please don't hit it to me".
我也是这个感觉
That's how I feel!
敢打来你就死定了
I'm gonna get you back!